Guide to the Walt Horan Papers 1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 8: Political, 1942-1964
  - Patronage
    - 1952-1960 (Box 450, Folder 8009)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 450, Folder 8010)
    - 1949-1957 (Box 450, Folder 8011)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 450, Folder 8012)
    - 1951-1956: Army-Navy Football Tickets (Box 450, Folder 8013)
    - 1956-1957: Army-Navy Football Tickets (Box 451, Folder 8014)
    - 1960-1964: Army-Navy Football Tickets (Box 451, Folder 8015)
    - 1959-1963: Army-Navy Football Tickets (Box 451, Folder 8016)
    - 1957-1963 (Box 451, Folder 8017)
    - 1949-1964 (Box 451, Folder 8018)
  - Travels
    - 1950-1951: Panama Trip Christmas 1950 (Box 451, Folder 8019)
    - 1950: President's Trip-Grand Coulee and 5th District (Box 451, Folder 8020)
    - 1949: Apple Blossom Trip West (Box 451, Folder 8021)
    - 1949-1950: Mexico, West Coast, and District Trip (Box 452, Folder 8022)
    - 1949: Mexico, West Coast, and District Trip (Box 452, Folder 8023)
    - 1949: Overseas Trip: Paris, Brussels, Frankfurt, Berlin (Box 452, Folder 8024-8025)
    - 1948-1949: Summer Trip-Invitations, etc. (Box 452, Folder 8026)
    - 1947: Trip West (Box 452, Folder 8027)
    - 1952: Columbia Basin Trip West (Box 453, Folder 8028)
    - 1952: Trip to London-attending wheat agreement conferences (Box 453, Folder 8029)
    - 1951-1952: Trip West (Box 453, Folder 8030-8031)
    - 1951: Trip West (Box 453, Folder 8032-8033)
    - 1951: Trip West, Mike's wedding (Box 453, Folder 8034)
    - 1953: Trip to District (Box 453, Folder 8035-8036)
    - 1953: Walt's OFAS Overseas Report (Box 454, Folder 8037-8039)
    - 1953: Trip to Europe (Box 454, Folder 8040-8041)
    - 1955: Highway Dedication Trip (Box 454, Folder 8042)
    - 1955: Highway Dedication Trip (continued) (Box 455, Folder 8043-8044)
    - 1955: Farm Forum Trip-Spokane (Box 455, Folder 8045)
    - 1955: Florida Trip (Box 455, Folder 8046-8047)
    - 1954: Hawaiian Trip, Joe Farrington's Funeral (Box 455, Folder 8048)
    - 1954: Trip to Florida, Week-end Dedication (Box 455, Folder 8049)
    - 1954: Trip to Florida (Box 455, Folder 8050)
    - 1956: Agriculture, Grange Speech (Box 455, Folder 8051-8052)
    - 1956: Trip West, Chief Joe Dedication and Whitworth College (Box 455, Folder 8053-8054)
    - 1956: Farm Forum Trip (Box 456, Folder 8055)
    - 1955: Trip to District (Box 456, Folder 8056-8058)
    - 1955: Pacific Northwest Trip for dam dedications and observations (Box 456, Folder 8059)
    - 1958: Trip on Santa Rosa (Box 456, Folder 8060)
    - 1958: Trip West (Box 456, Folder 8061)
    - 1958-1959: Panama Trip (Box 456, Folder 8062)
    - 1957: Trip West (Box 456, Folder 8063-8065)
    - 1957: American University-Beirut, Speech made to Lion's club (Box 457, Folder 8066)
    - 1957: Trip to New York, SS Matsonia (Box 457, Folder 8067)
    - 1957: Trip to Lancaster, PA, Franklin and Marshall College (Box 457, Folder 8068)
    - 1957: Farm Forum Trip to Spokane and Wenatchee (Box 457, Folder 8069)
    - 1957: Hawaii Trip (Box 457, Folder 8070)
    - 1961-1962: Trip West (Box 457, Folder 8071)
    - 1961: Trip West (Box 457, Folder 8072)
    - 1961: Trip to Dallas, TX, address NRECA Convention (Box 457, Folder 8073)
    - 1959-1960: Trip West (Box 457, Folder 8074)
    - 1959: Trip West (Box 457, Folder 8075)
    - 1959: Saratoga Trip (Box 458, Folder 8076)
    - 1959: Lilac Festival Trip (Box 458, Folder 8077)
    - 1960: Trip to Far East (Box 458, Folder 8078)
    - 1959: Agriculture Appropriations Trip (Box 458, Folder 8079)
    - 1960-1961: Miscellaneous Documents (Box 458, Folder 8080-8081)
    - 1960: Miscellaneous Documents (Box 458, Folder 8082)
    - 1960-1961: Trip around the world (Box 458, Folder 8083-8084)
    - 1960: Trip around the world (Box 458, Folder 8085)
    - 1960-1961: Mail about Overseas trip (Box 459, Folder 8086)
    - 1960-1961: A view of the U.S. wheat industry for Japanese wheat mission (Box 459, Folder 8087-8088)
    - 1961: Trip around the World Report (Box 459, Folder 8089)
    - 1962: Trip to New Haven, CT-observation of submarine base and Tullibee at Gorton, CT (Box 459, Folder 8090)
    - 1963: District Trip, Gonzaga Honorary Degree, county commissioners meeting, speeches, etc. (Box 459, Folder 8091-8093)
    - 1962: Trip West and Return, SS Taft via Panama, L.A. to N.Y. (Box 460, Folder 8094)
    - 1963: Rocky Reach dedication (Box 460, Folder 8095)
    - 1963: Pictures of Eisenhower (Box 460, Folder 8096)
    - 1964: Trip Home: Dedication of Forest Lab in Wenatchee, GOP Dinner, Spokane and Recreation conference (Box 460, Folder 8097-8099)
    - 1963: Trip Home "Go Rally" (Box 460, Folder 8100)
    - 1964: Panama Trip following General Election (Box 460, Folder 8101)
    - 1964: Trip Home prior to Primary (Box 460, Folder 8102)
    - 1964: Wenatchee Grange Diamond Jubilee, Walt's Address (Box 460, Folder 8103-8104)
  - Newspaper Clippings
    - Disabled Vets-Academy Appointments-Indian Claims (Box 461, Folder 8105)
    - Aluminum-Metal-Fraser (Box 461, Folder 8106)
    - Apples-GPG-Soft Fruit (Box 461, Folder 8107)
    - Horan-Regan-Miscellaneous (Box 461, Folder 8108)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 461, Folder 8109-8111)
    - 1944: Trip Abroad (Box 461, Folder 8112-8113)
    - 1944: Sally (Box 461, Folder 8114)
    - 1944: May and July Trips (Box 461, Folder 8115-8116)
    - 1944: Filing for Candidates-Political Friends (Box 461, Folder 8117)
    - 1944: Politics-Editorial (Box 461, Folder 8118)
    - Power-Ref. 2-Sweden of USA (Box 461, Folder 8119-8120)
    - CVA (Box 462, Folder 8121)
    - Mining Miscellaneous (Box 462, Folder 8122)
    - Ford-OPD (Box 462, Folder 8123)
    - Politics-Primary Vote 1944 and Misc (Box 462, Folder 8124)
    - Politics-Voting Record (Box 462, Folder 8125)
    - Unsorted 1 (Box 462, Folder 8126)
    - Unsorted 2 (Box 462, Folder 8127)
    - Unsorted 3 (Box 462, Folder 8128)
    - 1946-1947: Pacific Press Bureau (Box 462, Folder 8129)
    - Unsorted 4 (Box 462, Folder 8130)
    - Unsorted 5 (Box 462, Folder 8131)
    - Unsorted 6 (Box 463, Folder 8132)
    - Unsorted 7 (Box 463, Folder 8133)
    - Unsorted 8 (Box 463, Folder 8134)
    - Unsorted 9 (Box 463, Folder 8135)
    - Unsorted 10 (Box 463, Folder 8136)
    - Unsorted 11 (Box 463, Folder 8137)
    - Unsorted 12 (Box 464, Folder 8138)
    - 1946: Pacific Press Bureau (Box 464, Folder 8139-8140)
    - Unsorted 13 (Box 464, Folder 8141)
    - Unsorted 14 (Box 464, Folder 8142)
    - Unsorted 15 (Box 464, Folder 8143)
    - Unsorted 16 (Box 464, Folder 8144)
    - Unsorted 17 (Box 464, Folder 8145)
    - Unsorted 18 (Box 464, Folder 8146)
    - Unsorted 19 (Box 465, Folder 8147)
    - Unsorted 20 (Box 465, Folder 8148)
    - Unsorted 21 (Box 465, Folder 8149)
    - Unsorted 22 (Box 465, Folder 8150)
    - Unsorted 23 (Box 465, Folder 8151)
    - Unsorted 24 (Box 465, Folder 8152)
    - Unsorted 25 (Box 465, Folder 8153)
    - Unsorted 26 (Box 466, Folder 8154)
    - Unsorted 27 (Box 466, Folder 8155)
    - Unsorted 28 (Box 466, Folder 8156)
    - Unsorted 29 (Box 466, Folder 8157)
    - Unsorted 30 (Box 466, Folder 8158)
    - Unsorted 31 (Box 466, Folder 8159)
    - Unsorted 32 (Box 466, Folder 8160)
    - Unsorted 33 (Box 466, Folder 8161)
    - Unsorted 34 (Box 466, Folder 8162)
    - Unsorted 35 (Box 467, Folder 8163)
    - Unsorted 36 (Box 467, Folder 8164)
    - Unsorted 37 (Box 467, Folder 8165)
    - Unsorted 38 (Box 467, Folder 8166)
    - 1963: Goldmark Suit (Binder) (Box 467, Folder 8167-8170)
  - Photograph file
    - Miscellaneous photos, Horan family (Box 468, Folder 8171)
    - Events outside of Washington, D.C. (Box 468, Folder 8172)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 468, Folder 8173)
    - Constituent issues (Box 468, Folder 8174)
    - Washington, D.C. photographs of Horan with others, including colleagues, President Eisenhower, Vice President Nixon, Mrs. Horan, and visiting constituents (Box 468, Folder 8175-8179)
    - Washington, D.C. photographs (continued) (Box 469, Folder 8180)
    - Horan Publicity, Headshots (Box 469, Folder 8181)
    - 1945: Tour of Europe (Box 469, Folder 8182)
    - Aircraft Photos (Box 469, Folder 8183)
    - Public Speaking (Box 469, Folder 8184)
    - Western Dams (Box 469, Folder 8185)
    - Constituent Issues (Box 469, Folder 8186)
    - Events outside Washington, D.C. (Box 469, Folder 8187)
    - 1950: Sesquicentennial Events (Box 469, Folder 8188)
    - Constituents in Washington, D.C. (Box 469, Folder 8189)
    - Work on Capitol Hill and miscellaneous (Box 469, Folder 8190-8191)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous (Box 469, Folder 8192)
- Series 9: Extension 1, 1942-1951 (materials added to collection after initial processing)
  - Personal Correspondence
    - 1942 (Box 470, Folder 8193-8194)
    - 1943: General (Box 470, Folder 8195)
    - 1942-1944: Thank You Letters (Box 470, Folder 8196)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 470, Folder 8197)
    - 1942 (Box 470, Folder 8198-8200)
  - Outgoing Office Correspondence
    - 1942-1943: A-B (Box 471, Folder 8201)
    - 1942-1943: C-D (Box 471, Folder 8202)
    - 1942-1943: E-F (Box 471, Folder 8203)
    - 1942-1943: G-H (Box 471, Folder 8204)
    - 1942-1943: I-K (Box 471, Folder 8205)
    - 1942-1943: L-M (Box 471, Folder 8206)
    - 1942-1943: N-P (Box 471, Folder 8207)
    - 1942-1943: R-S (Box 472, Folder 8208)
    - 1942-1943: T-Z (Box 472, Folder 8209)
  - District of Columbia
    - Juvenile Court, 1948-1949 (Box 472, Folder 8210)
    - National Guard Armory, 1948 (Box 472, Folder 8211)
    - 1948-1949: Health (Box 472, Folder 8212)
    - 1948-1949: Recreation (Box 472, Folder 8213)
    - 1948-1949: Sales Tax (Box 472, Folder 8214)
    - 1948-1949: Police (Box 472, Folder 8215)
    - 1948-1949: Board of Trade (Box 472, Folder 8216)
    - 1948-1949: Alcoholic Clinic (Box 472, Folder 8217)
    - 1948-1949: Home Rule (Box 472, Folder 8218)
    - 1948-1949: Budget (Box 472, Folder 8219)
    - 1948-1949: Budget (Box 473, Folder 8220)
    - 1948-1949: Schools (Box 473, Folder 8221-8222)
    - 1948-1949: Hospitals (Box 473, Folder 8223)
    - 1947-1949: Veterans Services Center (Box 473, Folder 8224)
    - 1948-1949: Vehicles and Traffic (Box 473, Folder 8225)
    - 1948-1949: Sanitary Engineering (Box 473, Folder 8226)
    - 1948-1949: Dept. of Construction (Box 473, Folder 8227)
    - 1948-1949: Subcommittee Hearings (Box 473, Folder 8228-8229)
    - 1948-1949: Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 474, Folder 8230)
    - 1945-1947: Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 474, Folder 8231)
    - 1943-1945: Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 474, Folder 8232)
    - 1947: Correspondence: Personal Letters (Box 474, Folder 8233)
    - 1947-1948: Correspondence: Personal Letters (Box 474, Folder 8234)
    - 1947: Walt's Formula Bill and Correspondence (Box 474, Folder 8235)
  - Legislation
    - 1948: D.C. Legislation (Box 475, Folder 8236)
    - 1947: D.C. Legislation (Box 475, Folder 8237-8239)
    - 1943: D.C. Legislation (Box 475, Folder 8240)
    - 1942: D.C. Legislation (Box 475, Folder 8241)
    - 1950-1951: Farm Policy Legislation (Box 475, Folder 8242)
    - 1949-1950: Farm Policy Legislation (Box 475, Folder 8243)
    - 1949: Farm Policy Legislation (Box 476, Folder 8244-8246)
  - 1942-1946: Campaign materials (Box 476, Folder 8247)
  - 1942: Primary (Box 476, Folder 8248)
  - 1942-1943: Campaign materials (Box 476, Folder 8249)
  - Miscellaneous Campaign materials (Box 476, Folder 8250-8252)
  - Unsorted Newspaper clippings (Box 477, Folder 8253)
  - Grand Coulee Dam Stamps (Box 477, Folder 8254)
- Series 10: Extension 2, 1943-1964 (materials added to collection after initial processing)
  - Personal Correspondence
    - 1943 (Box 477, Folder 8255)
    - 1943-1946 (Box 477, Folder 8256)
    - 1944 (Box 477, Folder 8257)
    - 1945 (Box 477, Folder 8258-8260)
    - 1946 (Box 478, Folder 8261-8264)
    - 1947 (Box 478, Folder 8265-8267)
    - 1947 (continued) (Box 479, Folder 8268)
    - 1948 (Box 479, Folder 8269-8273)
    - 1949 (Box 479, Folder 8274)
    - 1949 (continued) (Box 480, Folder 8275-8277)
    - 1950 (Box 480, Folder 8278-8280)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 481, Folder 8281-8284)
    - 1953 (Box 481, Folder 8285-8287)
    - 1954 (Box 482, Folder 8288-8290)
    - 1956 (Box 482, Folder 8291-8293)
    - 1958 (Box 482, Folder 8294)
    - 1958 (continued) (Box 483, Folder 8295-8298)
    - 1959 (Box 483, Folder 8299-8302)
    - 1959 (continued) (Box 484, Folder 8303)
    - 1960 (Box 484, Folder 8304-8306)
    - 1961 (Box 484, Folder 8307-8308)
    - 1961 (continued) (Box 485, Folder 8309-8310)
    - 1962 (Box 485, Folder 8311-8315)
    - 1963 (Box 486, Folder 8316-8321)
    - 1964 (Box 486, Folder 8322)
    - 1964 (Box 487, Folder 8323-8326)
  - Personal invitations
    - 1947 (Box 487, Folder 8327)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 487, Folder 8328)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 488, Folder 8329)
    - 1943-1945 (Box 488, Folder 8330)
    - 1948 (Box 488, Folder 8331-8333)
    - 1949 (Box 488, Folder 8334-8335)
    - 1949 (continued) (Box 489, Folder 8336)
    - 1950 (Box 489, Folder 8337-8339)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 489, Folder 8340-8342)
    - 1951-1952 (continued) (Box 490, Folder 8343-8344)
    - 1953 (Box 490, Folder 8345-8347)
    - 1954 (Box 490, Folder 8348)
    - 1954 (continued) (Box 491, Folder 8349-8350)
    - 1955 (Box 491, Folder 8351-8353)
    - 1958 (Box 491, Folder 8354-8355)
    - 1958 (continued) (Box 492, Folder 8356-8357)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 492, Folder 8358)
    - 1959 (Box 492, Folder 8359-8362)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 493, Folder 8363)
    - 1960 (Box 493, Folder 8364-8367)
    - 1961 (Box 493, Folder 8368-8369)
    - 1961 (continued) (Box 494, Folder 8370-8371)
    - 1962 (Box 494, Folder 8372-8375)
    - 1963 (Box 495, Folder 8376-8380)
    - 1964 (Box 495, Folder 8381-8382)
    - 1964 (continued) (Box 496, Folder 8383-8385)
  - Family correspondence
    - 1949 (Box 496, Folder 8386-8387)
    - 1950 (Box 496, Folder 8388)
    - 1951 (Box 497, Folder 8389)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 497, Folder 8390-8391)
    - 1953 (Box 497, Folder 8392-8393)
    - 1955 (Box 497, Folder 8394-8395)
    - 1956 (Box 498, Folder 8396)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 498, Folder 8397-8399)
    - 1958 (Box 498, Folder 8400-8401)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 499, Folder 8402)
    - 1960 (Box 499, Folder 8403)
    - 1961 (Box 499, Folder 8404)
    - 1962 (Box 499, Folder 8405)
    - 1963 (Box 499, Folder 8406-8407)
    - 1964 (Box 499, Folder 8408)
  - Personal Correspondence
    - General (Includes some ephemera) (Box 500, Folder 8409)
    - General (Box 500, Folder 8410-8411)
    - Letters from friends (Box 500, Folder 8412)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 500, Folder 8413)
    - 1947-1948: Sally Horan (Box 500, Folder 8414)
    - Miscellaneous: "Very interesting" (Box 500, Folder 8415)
    - Sally Horan (Box 500, Folder 8416)
    - Lillian Siegler (Box 500, Folder 8417)
    - 1964: Letters when in hospital after the election (Box 500, Folder 8418)
    - Consolation notes: Gammie (Mrs. Margaret Horan) (Box 500, Folder 8419)
    - Christmas Letters (Box 500, Folder 8420)
    - Mrs. Notewane (Box 500, Folder 8421)
    - Walt's jokes and poems (Box 501, Folder 8422-8424)
    - Questions for speeches (Box 501, Folder 8425)
    - Speeches (Box 501, Folder 8426)
    - 1946: Primary Campaign (Box 501, Folder 8427)
    - Record of publication in papers (Box 501, Folder 8428)
    - Men's Bible class (Box 501, Folder 8429)
    - Clyde Kelly Bible class correspondence (Box 501, Folder 8430-8432)
    - Loose and unlabeled items (Box 502, Folder 8433)
    - Scrapbook: honorary luncheon (Box 502, Folder 8434)
    - Gridiron Dinner (Box 502, Folder 8435)
    - 1959: Sig Ep Lunch for Walter Rogers (Thursday May 21) (Box 502, Folder 8436)
    - Burning Tree Country Club (Box 502, Folder 8437)
    - Army Navy Club (Box 502, Folder 8438)
    - Breakfast Club (Box 502, Folder 8439)
    - Lion's Club Correspondence, etc (Box 502, Folder 8440)
    - Schedule (1959) (Box 502, Folder 8441)
    - 1953: Capitol Hill Club (Box 502, Folder 8442)
    - 1945: Overseas Trip (Box 503, Folder 8443)
    - Pictures overseas trip (Box 503, Folder 8444)
    - Income Tax check 1949, 1950, 1953 (Trip) (Box 503, Folder 8445)
    - Personal-Germany-Cradle shipment (Box 503, Folder 8446)
    - Royal Daulton Figurines (Box 503, Folder 8447)
    - Automobile papers, gasoline rationing, etc (Box 503, Folder 8448)
    - 1953: Chevy Chase Parking (Box 503, Folder 8449)
    - Automobile papers (Box 503, Folder 8450-8452)
  - Campaign scrapbooks: 1940, 1943-1944 (Box 504)
  - Campaign scrapbooks: 1940, Overseas scrapbooks, 1945 (Box 505)
  - 1945: European Trip (and maybe some 1953) (Box 506, Folder 8453-8458)
  - 1945: European Trip (and maybe some 1953) (Box 507, Folder 8459-8461)
  - 1945: European Trip (and maybe some 1953) (Box 507, Folder 8462-8464)
  - 1945: European Trip (Box 507, Folder 8465-8466)
  - 1946: Campaign scrapbook and 1946-1947 clipping scrapbook (Box 508)
  - 1946-1948: Clippings and campaign scrapbooks (Box 509)
  - 1952-1954: Campaign scrapbooks (Box 510)
  - 1956-1958: Campaign Scrapbooks (Box 511)
  - 1957-1963: Clippings of Horan portraits (Box 512)
  - 1962-1964: Clippings of Horan portraits (Box 513)
  - 1964: Cards received in hospital (Box 514, Folder 8467-8469)
  - Clippings and other material: photographs, correspondence (Box 515, Folder 8470)
  - 1948-1949: Clippings and other materials (Box 515, Folder 8471)
  - 1945-1949: Clippings and other materials (Box 515, Folder 8472)
  - 1940-1950: Clippings and other materials: invitations, correspondence, ephemera (Box 515, Folder 8473)
  - 1949-1958: Clippings and other materials: Invitation, Truman inauguration, clippings, miscellaneous ephemera (Box 515, Folder 8474)
  - 1949-1951: Clippings and other materials: Event programs and other ephemera, correspondence and clippings (Box 515, Folder 8475)
  - 1944-1947: Clippings and other materials: Correspondence, clippings, ephemera (Box 515, Folder 8476)
  - 1949-1950: Clippings and other materials (Box 515, Folder 8477)
  - 1945-1950: Clippings and other materials (continued) (Box 515, Folder 8478)
  - Clippings and other materials: Photographs, fruit box labels (Horan bros. and others) (Box 515, Folder 8479)
- Series 11: Oversize (location note: map case)
  - Map, Okanogan County, WA. Printed map published by the Department of Highways, 1939. Enhanced with hand-colored markings indicating the following areas: National Forest Lands, Colville Indian Lands, Federal Power--Grand Coulee Dam, Omak Flight Strip, Scho (Box Oversize, Folder (map case))